{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Gottlieb",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "Actor, comedian, screenwriter",
    "human_readable": "Carl Gottlieb's occupation is Actor, comedian, screenwriter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9338652491569519,
            "question": "Carl Gottlieb is a screenwriter. What does this mean?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.801496148109436,
            "question": "What are some of Carl Gottlieb's professions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440755367279053,
            "question": "Can you name a movie where Carl Gottlieb has acted and written?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7358881831169128,
            "question": "What are some examples of Carl Gottlieb's work as an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7345527410507202,
            "question": "Has Carl Gottlieb written any famous movies or shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7118483781814575,
            "question": "What is Carl Gottlieb known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.693642795085907,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other roles has Carl Gottlieb played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658759713172913,
            "question": "What makes someone a successful actor, comedian, and screenwriter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6409198641777039,
            "question": "Does Carl Gottlieb work in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49452558159828186,
            "question": "How might Carl Gottlieb's different roles complement each other?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Gottlieb's occupation is Actor, comedian, screenwriter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5560_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Carl Gottlieb work in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5560_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes someone a successful actor, comedian, and screenwriter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5560_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides acting, what other roles has Carl Gottlieb played?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5560_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5560_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Carl Gottlieb being an American screenwriter, actor, and comedian. Therefore, the statement that his occupations include actor, comedian, and screenwriter is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}